Hello everyone, welcome back to our PostgreSQL tutorial series.
So, today we are going to explore the where in the PostgreSQL SQL.
So, first of all simply explain for the where PostgreSQL allows us to apply the condition
to filter the function table based on the specific criteria.
And it's a powerful tool for it to having only the data that meets the certain requirement
to explore how it works with some examples. So, first of all here we spoke the simple
oil flow. So, here define for the select star. And now we are choose for the
employees. Now, here I can use first the wire close. This is the department. So,
is the department is equal to. So, here perfect use for the IT and use for the
silica statement all columns from the employee stable and where the department column is equal
to IT. And now first of all here select this data query and the next queue. And you can see here
that food for the operation is perfectly successful. And PostgreSQL will return the
condition and department of output. Okay, I hope you perfectly understand it.
Now, just here for the next example. So, here here this multiple condition with the
board close. Okay. So, here I can use for the department of. So, now just type for the department
of age. Okay. And now here just apply for the end operator. And now just here we create for
the salary. So, define for the salary is greater than 50,000. Okay. So, now just here you can
verify. And execute you can see here not define this one. Okay. So, now just change for the
use for the less than and just check the queue. And you can see here less than 50. And here
salary is 40,000 and the department of the teacher. Okay. And I hope you perfectly understand
this operation perfectly successful. And here the PostgreSQL will return all the row. That
means the condition in the required set. So, here I can open for another operator. So, here
is for the comparison operator with the wire close. So, here the operation will perfectly use
the wire close. So, here open for this and now only using for the age. Okay. So, define for the age.
And define here the age is greater than for now here define for the age is 27. Okay. And
here I can use for the age is 32. Okay. So, define this perfectly and here perfectly use the wire
close to select from the employee stable with the age column is greater than 32. Okay.
So, here I am going to select an execute and you can see here the result for the
employment, dividend age is the 35 and here the department. And I hope it is completely working
this example and here also going for another example just pattern matching with the wire close.
So, now just type for the user, wire close and select the employees from the employee stable
and move on to lastly man. Just employees name and now here just apply
user life operator. Okay. So, first of all here type this last name. Okay. Then use this is
the life operator and then single position inside create first of all the module. Okay. So, first
I can type this and the model because it is the last name. Okay. And now here completely create
then execute. Okay. So, you can see here the last name of the son and here the department of son.
Okay. Now, just check for here use for the employee stable and now here use for the
board and I can mark the character of J and just select an execute. You can see here open for
the employee of another employee name. The this on the salary is 45,000 and the department of the
marketing. Okay. So, here I have perfectly applied for the pattern matching with the wire close.
Okay. So, here this session is perfectly done and I have perfectly reviewed the using of the wire
close in the post grade school with some practical example. Okay. So, I hope you perfectly understand
this session. So, and I hope you find this tutorial helpful. So, stay tuned for more post grade
SQL tips and clicks. Okay. So, thank you for watching.